{"data":[{"question":"John's ________ improved at his new school.","a":"behave","b":"behavioral","c":"behavior","d":"behaviorism","answer":"3","explain":"\n- After possessive form ('s) is a noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Jim always does what he says; he's a very ________ person.","a":"rely","b":"reliably","c":"reliance","d":"reliable","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Very + adj\/avd.\u00a0\n- To be (is) + adj.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The company is very efficient and gives a ________ service.","a":"speed","b":"speeding","c":"speedy","d":"speediness","answer":"3","explain":"\n- A + adj + noun (noun phrase).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Dogs are very ________ pets.","a":"faith","b":"faithful","c":"faithfully","d":"faithfulness","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Very + adj\/avd.\u00a0\n- To be (is) + adj.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Since ________ has been so poor, the class has to be closed.","a":"attend","b":"attendant","c":"attendance","d":"attendee","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Subject is often noun\/pronoun.\u00a0\n- Attendance: the number of people attend a meeting\/class...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you have a ________ costume in your country?","a":"national","b":"nation","c":"native","d":"nationality","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A + adj + noun (noun phrase).\u00a0\n- Native : is place smaller than national.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The weather will be better with ________ showers.","a":"occasion","b":"occasional","c":"occasionally","d":"occasionality","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Adj + Noun (noun phrase).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"I had no map. That's why I got lost. If I ________ a map, I ________ all right.","a":"have \/ will be","b":"had \/ would be","c":"had had \/ would have been","d":"a & b are correct","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 3: If + past perfect, would\/could\/should + have + PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"Most people ________ the Union meeting if they had had longer notice of it.","a":"would have attended","b":"would attend","c":"will attend","d":"shall attend","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Conditional sentence type 3: If + past perfect, would\/could\/should + have + PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"},{"question":"The boy with his dog ________ here last night.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n-The phrase introduced by as well as or along with will modify the earlier word (the boy).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"27","type":"1"}]}